Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ho-yuan-ai (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Data Analytics
Software Development
Intelligent Systems

Languages

Chinese (Native or Bilingual)
Malay (Limited Working)
English (Professional Working)

Honors-Awards
Cliff Bellamy Award (First Year)

Yuan Ai Ho

Computer Science Graduate Selangor

Summary

I am a fresh graduate in Computer Science. In a nutshell, I am interested and have had experience in software development, data science and web application development. With good logical thinking and analytical skills, I love to solve complicated problems. Motivated by coffee and cats.

Experience

Monash University Malaysia Research Assistant August 2020 - December 2020 (5 months)

Indoor location analytics using unsupervised machine learning methods

Public Bank Information Technology Intern December 2019 - February 2020 (3 months) Kajang, Selangor, Malaysia

- Actively involved in a website development project
- Design user interface using HTML5, CSS3 and JQuery
- Build web using ASP .NET framework following the MVC design pattern
- · Database design and queries using Microsoft SQL Server

Education

Monash University Malaysia

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science (2018 - 2020)

Kolej Methodist Kuala Lumpur (MCKL) Cambridge GCE A-Levels · (2016 - 2017)